（香苗）桜井
せっかく滑りにきたんだから
Sakurai!
We came all the way out here to skate, so let's skate together.
一緒に滑ろうよ
（梨穂子）うッ　うん
Y... Yeah...
Come on, I'll even hold your hand for you.
ほら　ちゃんと手
持っててあげるから
わあッ
ハハハッ　ダメみたい
It's no use...
しょうがないな～
You're hopeless.
あッ　お～い　橘君！
Hey, Tachibana-kun!
What is it, Kanae-san?
（純一）どうしたの？　香苗さん
Do something about Sakurai here.
ちょっと桜井のこと
何とかしてやってよ
うん？
えッ？
All right.
しょうがないなあ
だッ　大丈夫…
I-I'm fine.
S... See?
ほッ　ほら
わあッ　わッ　わッ！
W-Whoa, Sakurai!
ちょっと　桜井
うわ～ッ
コラ～ッ
Hey!
What are you doing?
何やってるんだよ～
Waah, it's so cold!
うわ～ん　冷た～い
Of course it is.
そりゃ当たり前だよ
まったく　体を動かすために
来たんだろ？
Sheesh.
Didn't you come here to exercise?
You haven't been moving around at all.
全然　動いてないじゃないか
But... I'll fall.
だって　転んじゃうんだもん
Well, you've always been bad at skating, Rihoko.
梨穂子は昔から
スケート　ダメだったもんな
Tachibana-kun, you take it from here.
橘君　あとよろしくね～
Ah, Kanae-chan!
あッ　香苗ちゃん
Come on.
ほら
Gimme your hand.
手　貸せよ
いいよ
I'm fine.
遠慮するなよ
Don't be shy.
I'm not being shy...
別に遠慮とかじゃないよ
I can practice on my own.
練習くらい　１人でできるから
Hey now...
おいおい
うわッ　あれあれ…
うわッ　ああッ
危ないッ
I-I-I'm gonna hit somebody!
ぶッ　ぶつかる～ッ
ああ～ッ　どいてどいて
Move, move...
There you go.  You're fine.
はいはい　大丈夫よ
うわ～ッ
いッ！
うわ～ッ！
ごめん！
Sorry!
うわあッ！
いたたた～ッ
R-Rihoko...
梨穂子
何？　純一
What is it, Junichi?
見えてるぞ
I can see them.
えッ？
No!
やだ～ッ　純一のエッチ！
Junichi, you pervert!
You're the one who had them on display!
梨穂子が見せたんだろ
I wasn't showing them on purpose.
見せてないもん
It's your fault for falling.
梨穂子が転ぶから悪いんだよ
That's not...
そんなあ
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
・～
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
Sakurai Rihoko Arc
Chapter 2
Help
さっき転んだのは
なかなか高ポイントだったね～
That fall was worth a lot of points!
えッ　どういうこと？　香苗ちゃん
Huh?
What do you mean, Kanae-chan?
さっき橘君　不可抗力とはいえ
桜井の胸をつかんで
It's true that Tachibana-kun couldn't avoid it, but don't
you think he really reacted when he grabbed your chest?
グラッときてると思うな～
No, he definitely reacted.
いや　きてないはずがない
ええッ　胸って…
My chest...?
よし　今後の作戦を立てようよ
All right, let's plan your next move!
作戦って？
My next move?
いいから　いいから
Don't worry about it.
Just leave it to me!
私に任せなさいって
Let's see...
そうだな　創設祭も近いし
キャンプファイヤーで…
The Founder's Festival is coming soon.  Maybe at the campfire...
ムフフフ…
T-Thank you, Kanae-chan.
ありがとう　香苗ちゃん
But I'll be busy at the festival with Tea Club activities.
でも　私　創設祭は
茶道部で忙しいから
あッ　そっか
Oh, I see...
Hey!
（梅原）おーい　写真撮ろうぜ
Let's take a picture!
Yeah, sure!
うん　いいよ
楽しかったな　スケート
Skating was really fun.
Huh?  What happened to your gloves, Junichi?
《あれ？　純一　手袋どうしたの？》
Oh, I lost them not too long ago.
《ああ　こないだ
なくしちゃったんだ》
I wonder if I'll make it before Christmas...
クリスマスまでに間に合うかなあ
茶道部です
I'm from the Tea Club.
創設祭の　備品貸し出しの
申請をお願いします
I'd like a Founder's Festival
equipment rental application, please.
Okay.
（詞）はい　じゃあ
この申請書に記入してね
Just fill out this form here.
あのう
何？
Um...
Yes?
What should I write?
どう書けばいいのかな？
使用したい備品を書いてくれる？
Could you write what equipment you need to borrow?
何がいるんだろう？
I wonder what we need...
えッ？
梨穂子の結構大きかったな
Rihoko's chest was pretty big...
この　まんま肉まんくらいか
About as big as this meat bun?
About this big?
このくらいだったっけ？
No, Rihoko's were even bigger.
いや　梨穂子のはこんなもんじゃ…
（琉璃子）うん？
（愛歌）あッ
・（琉璃子）おい　そこの
肉まんもみながら→
Hey, you there who's daydreaming and blushing while squeezing a meat bun.
ボーッと赤くなっているやつ
えッ？
Your name's Tachibana Junichi, right?
確か橘純一とか言ったっけ？
ちょっとつきあえ
Come with us for a bit.
どうして僕の名前を？
How do you know my name?
あの　どちら様ですか？
Um... who are you?
Sakurai Rihoko.
桜井梨穂子
どう見ても違うじゃないですか
I find that pretty hard to believe...
You sure like to nitpick on little details for a guy.
男のクセに
細かいことをブチブチと
うるさいやつめ
ええッ？
Whiny little fellow.
いいから　つきあうのか？
つきあわないのか？
So are you gonna help us or not?
どっちだ？
What'll it be?
あの　僕
何につきあえばいいんですか？
Um... what can I do for you?
ちょっと　これ運ぶの
手伝ってくれないか？
Could you help us carry this?
What is it?
これって？
A giant fish cake.
巨大はんぺんだ
I just need to help you carry the top of your kotatsu, right?
コタツの天板を運ぶの
手伝えばいいんですね
ピンポン！
正解
Bingo.
Correct.
You're pretty quick on the uptake.
ものわかりがいいね
りほっちには眼力あり
Rihocchi has good tastes.
Uh... are you friends with Sakurai?
ええと　桜井の知り合いですか？
ああ　初めてだったね
Ah, so we haven't met before.
I'm the President of the Tea Club, Yuzuki Ruriko.
私は茶道部部長　夕月琉璃子だ
Hiba Manaka.  The Vice President.
飛羽愛歌　ザ・副部長
Oh, so you're the seniors from the Tea Club.
ああ　茶道部の先輩達ですか
案外重たいんだよね　これ
This is a lot heavier than I thought it would be.
もう疲れた
I'm tired already.
You should've just set it down while we were talking.
話している間は　下に置いておけば
いいんじゃないですか？
Aren't you clever?
うまいこと言うな
座布団５枚
You get five points.
（琉璃子・愛歌）おお～ッ
Thank you.
ご苦労さん
おっつ～
Good work~
いやあ
It's fine...
I'll make some tea, so please have some.
・（琉璃子）お茶くらい出すから
飲んでってくれ
But I don't really know the proper etiquette...
でも僕
作法とか　よく分からないです
・（琉璃子）
番茶に作法なんかあるのかい？
Is there etiquette for regular tea?
Never heard of it.
・（愛歌）初耳だ
I mean... you're the Tea Club and all, so I thought...
あッ　いえ
茶道部だから　てっきり
It's just lunch break, so it's not like we'll be making any high-end tea.
さすがに昼休みから
抹茶をたてたりはしないよ
I-I guess not.
そうですよね
Whoa, it's really good.
あッ　おいしいです
そうかい　ありがとう
Really?  Thanks.
そういえば
何で初対面なのに僕のこと
By the way, how did you know I'm Sakurai's friend even though we've never met?
桜井の知り合いだって
分かったんですか？
監視
えッ？
Surveillance.
What?!
冗談
Joke.
Well, Rihocchi talks about you all the time.
いや　りほっちが
あんたの話ばかりするのよ
耳にタコ
僕のことを？
Any more and we'd be deaf.
About me?
Um... what does she say about me?
あの　あいつ僕のこと
何て言ってました？
フフン
言えないってことは…
So it's something you can't say...
ハハハハッ
You sure have a lot of stuff here.
ここって色々　置いてありますね
Are they all for tea?
みんなお茶の道具ですか？
気に入ったかい？　この部屋が
Do you like this room?
PERSISTENCE YIELDS RESULTS
・（愛歌）茶道部が
えッ？
Or the Tea Club?
（扉が開く）
はあ～ッ　先輩
創設祭の申請書　出してきました
Senpai, I turned in the application for the Founder's Festival.
もうヘトヘトです
I'm completely worn out.
えッ？　純一　何でここに？
Junichi?  Why are you here?
よう
Y-Yo.
あれ？　絢辻先輩
どうしたんですか？
Huh, Ayatsuji-senpai?
What's wrong?  You look exhausted.
ずいぶんお疲れの様子ですけど
Ah, I'm fine.
ああ　大丈夫よ
茶道部の申請書を作るのが
ちょっと大変だったの
Filling out the application for the Tea Club was pretty tough.
えッ？
あはははは…
純一　これ運ぶの
手伝ってくれたんだ
Junichi, so you helped to carry this?
Yeah, it just happened.
成り行きだけどね
ありがとう
Thank you.
やっぱり　おこたはいいですね～
Kotatsu sure are nice.
ずっとこのまま　ここでこうして…
I could stay here like this forever...
（チャイム）
Time's up.
時間切れ
はい　残念賞
You get the consolation prize!
Come back after school.
続きは放課後にね
そんなあ
じゃあ僕　教室に戻ります
Aw, man...
Well, I'll be heading back now.
Ah, I'll come with you.
ああ　私も一緒に
Well then, excuse me.
それじゃ　失礼します
Ah, wait a minute.
ああ　ちょっと待った
はい？
Yes?
You really helped us out today, so I dunno about asking this...
今日は助かったよ
で　ついでと言っちゃ何だが
創設祭のときも
手伝ってくれないかい？
But could you help us out at the Founder's Festival too?
えッ？
ご覧のとおり　男手がないんだよ
As you can see, we have no guys in the club.
Us girls can't do much with our weak arms.
女の細腕じゃ心もとないし
力仕事を頼みたいんだがね
I was hoping you could help us with the muscle work.
はあ　まあ　僕でよかったら
ホント？
Right.
Well, if you don't mind me...
Really?
よしッ　じゃあ　そういうことで
頼んだよ
All right, let's do that.
We're counting on you.
はい　じゃあ失礼します
Okay.  Excuse me.
Excuse me!
失礼しま～す
純一が創設祭　手伝って
くれることになって　よかった
Junichi, I'm glad that you'll be
helping us for the Founder's Festival.
おもしろい先輩達だったな
Your seniors were pretty interesting.
Yeah.  They're good people.
うん　いい人達なんだよ
Looks like he's the one.
・（琉璃子）決まったな　彼に
The gods have chosen.
白羽の矢
For the sake of the Tea Club.
我らが茶道部のために
りほっちのために
For the sake of Rihocchi.
・～
Swim Club
Oden Stand Recipe
Secret Formula!!
これで明日の創設祭の準備は
大丈夫ですね
Now everything's ready for the Founder's Festival tomorrow.
ご苦労さんだったね　りほっち
Thank you, Rihocchi.
Good work~
おっつ～
えへへへへッ
あ～ッ　るっこ先輩のいれるお茶は
やっぱりおいしいですね
The tea you make really is delicious, Rukko-senpai.
フフン　持ち上げても何も出ないよ
Your flattery won't get you anything.
歯が浮く
Empty flattery.
やだなあ　お世辞じゃないですよ
Hey, it wasn't empty flattery.
だって私がいくら頑張っても
I mean, I can't make tea this good no matter how hard I try.
こんなにうまく
いれられないですもん
But Rihocchi, you'll need to make it for the underclassmen once we're gone.
でも私らがいなくなったら
りほっちが後輩に
いれてやらなきゃならないんだぞ
えッ？
とはいえ
Though... we don't have any of them, so I guess we don't need to worry.
その後輩がいないから
いらぬ心配か
チーン
Ding.
なあ　りほっち
Hey, Rihocchi.
今年の創設祭は
去年とは違うからね
This year's Founder's Festival won't be like last year's.
覚悟しておくように
えッ　何がですか？
Prepare yourself.
Huh?  For what?
新入部員　勧誘
ああ～
Member recruitment.
さすがに　りほっち１人だと
茶道部は廃部になりかねないから
After all, if it's just you, Rihocchi, the Tea Club will be disbanded.
私　頑張ります
I'll do my best!
I'll definitely keep the Tea Club going!
茶道部を絶対に守ります
いやまあ　そんなに
力を入れなくてもいいだろう
Whoa there...
There's no need to get that fired up.
とりあえず　お座り
Just sit down for now.
でね　ものは相談なんだが
はい
Well, there's something we want to discuss.
Yes?
Tachibana Junichi.
橘純一
はッ？
How about bringing him in as a new member?
彼を新入部員にするっていうのは
どうだろう？
J-Junichi as a new member?
純一を部員にですか？
・（琉璃子）この前　部室に来た時も
色々　興味持ってたようだしね
When he came here the other day, he seemed pretty interested.
Suitable.
・（愛歌）適任
そうなんですか？
You think so?
いいかい？　りほっち
Got it, Rihocchi?
Y... Yes...
えッ　ええ…
決定
It's decided.
でも　純一　入部してくれるかな？
But will Junichi really join?
あとは私達に任せろ
Leave that to us.
秘策あり
We have a plan.
Huh?  What are you gonna do, Senpai?
えッ　先輩
どうするつもりなんですか？
はあ　クリスマスイブか
Christmas Eve, huh?
（ドアが開く）
Nii-nii, what are you doing?
（美也）にぃに　何してるの？
うん？
今年は行くんじゃなかったの？
創設祭
Aren't you going to the Founder's Festival this year?
えッ？　ああ
梨穂ちゃんの茶道部を手伝うって
約束してるんでしょ
Didn't you promise to help Riho-chan and the Tea Club?
Yeah, you're right.
ああ　そうだったな
行くか
Guess I'll go.
・（美也）みゃー　待ち合わせ
してるから先に行くよ
I'm meeting up with a friend, so I'll head out first.
うん
Okay.
Kibitou High School
Founder's
Festival
見てろよ　数時間後に行われる
フォークダンスというゴールに
Just watch.
My goal is the folk dance that will take place in a few hours.
俺は必ず勝者として
立ってみせるぞ！
I'll definitely emerge victorious!
何だ　まだ諦めてなかったのか？
What?  You still haven't given up?
バカヤロー　俺の辞書に
諦めるという言葉は存在しない
Fool!
The verb "to give up" doesn't exist in my vocabulary!
I'll go all out and fight until the very last second!
最後の１秒まで　決して
手をゆるめず　戦い抜いてみせる
ああ　頑張ってくれ
Right, best of luck.
大将　俺の生き様を
しっかりその目に刻んでくれよ
Boss.
Watch carefully how I live my life!
Okay.
分かった
TEA  CLUB
遅くなりました
Sorry I'm late.
Ooh, you came just at the right time.
おお～
ちょうどいいところに来たね
じゃあ早速だけど
甘酒運ぶの手伝ってくれないか？
There's no time to waste.
Could you carry this sweet sake for us?
はい
Yes.
We serve sweet sake at the Tea Club every year.
・（琉璃子）毎年　茶道部で
甘酒を振る舞っていてね
Oh?
へえ～
これが結構重いんだ
It's pretty heavy.
ナイスタイミング
Nice timing.
You can have some tea and sweet sake as thanks afterwards.
あとでちゃんとお礼に
お茶と甘酒もごちそうするからね
Yes.  I'll do my best to help.
はい　しっかり
手伝わせてもらいますよ
ついに　あんたにも茶道部員の
自覚が出てきたみたいだね
It looks like you finally see yourself as a Tea club member.
部員じゃないです
残念
I'm not a member.
Pity.
・（琉璃子）いや～　さすが男の子
Wow, guys sure are different.
T-This is pretty heavy.
結構　重たいですね　これ
どこに置けばいいんですか？
Where should I set it down?
Over there would be good.
じゃあ　そこに置いてくれるかな
分かりました
Okay.
Thanks.  You saved us a lot of trouble.
あんがと　助かったよ
ああ　ついでに
何ですか？
Oh, by the way...
What is it?
How about joining the Tea Club?
茶道部に入部してみないか？
あはは　それはちょっと…
I don't know about that...
あれ？
純一　もう来てくれてたんだ
Huh?  Junichi, you're here already.
ちょっと　これ着るのに
時間かかって遅くなっちゃった
Putting this on took a while, so that's why I'm late.
りッ　梨穂子…
R-Rihoko...
What, Junichi?
何？　純一
You look... nice in a kimono.
和服　似合うじゃないか
私らも　さっきから和服だが？
You know, we're in kimonos too.
もちろん　お二人も似合ってますよ
They look great on you both too.
今さら
It's a little late for that.
次はチラシ配りを
お願いできるかい？
Can you help distribute the fliers next?
はい　分かりました
Okay, sure thing.
Well, Rihocchi, let him know what to do.
じゃあ　りほっち
教えてあげてくれ
こっちも人手が足りないから
早めに戻っておいで
We don't have enough people on our end either, so come back as soon as you can.
Roger!
了解です
創設祭って
色々やることがあるんだな
There's a lot to do at the Founder's Festival.
うん　そうだよ
Yep, that's right.
It was really tough for me last year
because I didn't know how to do anything.
去年は私　何も分からなくて
大変だったんだから
I'm glad both of my seniors were there for me.
ホント先輩達がいてくれて
よかった～
…って今年もそうなんだけどね
Though, that's also the case this year.
ねえ　純一
うん？
Hey, Junichi.
Why don't you take this opportunity to join the Tea Club?
この機会に茶道部に
入っちゃうってのは　どうかな
Hmm... I'm not really interested right now.
う～ん　今のところ
そこまでの興味はないかな
I see.
そっか
茶道部で甘酒ごちそうしてま～す
We're serving sweet sake at the Tea Club!
お庭でお茶会もやってま～す
We're also having a tea party on the grounds!
梨穂ちゃん
あッ　美也ちゃん
Riho-chan!
Ah, Miya-chan.
にぃに　役に立ってる？
うん
Is Nii-nii of any help?
Yeah, he really helped us out with the muscle work and stuff.
力仕事とか手伝ってもらって
助かってるよ
Oh?
へえ～　にぃにがねえ
Did he really?
うん
おい　美也
Hey, Miya.
僕だって　やるときは
やるんだからな
I get things done when I put my mind to it.
ほらッ
Here.
ねえ　紗江ちゃん
お茶会行ってみる？
Hey, Sae-chan.  Wanna go to the tea party?
（紗江）うん　行ってみたいけど
Yes, I do...
水泳部の逢ちゃんのおでん
なくならないかな
But I wonder if the Girls Swim Club's... Ai-chan's Oden stall will still be there.
あッ　そっか
じゃあ　おでんのあとにお茶だね
Ah, right.
Then let's have tea after some Oden.
Okay.
うん
じゃあ　あとで行くね
Well, we'll be there later.
Yeah, we'll be waiting!
うん　待ってるよ
I think I'll have Daikon and...
やっぱ大根と…
Miya!  Don't get carried away and eat too much!
美也ーッ
調子に乗って食べ過ぎるなよ
・（美也）うるさい　分かってます
You're annoying!  I know already!
Hey, Rihoko.
なあ　梨穂子
何？
What?
そろそろお茶会に
戻った方がいいんじゃ？
Shouldn't we be heading back to the Tea Club soon?
あっちも忙しくなってると思うし
I'd imagine that it's getting pretty busy over there.
そうだった
じゃあ　あとはよろしくね
You're right.
I'll leave the rest to you.
ああ　任しとけ
Yeah, leave it to me.
Well then, are you ready everyone?
（詞）それでは皆さん
準備はよろしいですか？
Yeah!
What?  What?
何だ　何だ？
何だろう？
What's going on?
It's coming from the gym.
体育館の方だ　行ってみよう
うん
Let's go see.
Yeah.
５　４　３　２　１
Five!  Four!
Three!  Two!  One!
ゼロ！
Zero!
It's beautiful.
キレイだな～
うん
Yeah.
梨穂子
うん？
Rihoko.
メリークリスマス
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス　純一
Merry Christmas, Junichi!
続いてのエントリーは
伊藤香苗さんです
Miss Santa Contest
Our next entrant is Itou Kanae-san!
Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス！
It's hot, so be careful.
Oden
Girl's
Swim Club
熱いから気をつけてね
Rihoko.
梨穂子
えッ　何？
What?
Don't you need to head back soon?
そろそろ戻らないと
いけないんじゃないか？
Oh no!
あッ　いけない　早く行かなきゃ
I'd better hurry!
転ぶなよ
ああ　うん
Don't fall over!
Y-Yeah...
わあッ
純一　今日はありがとうね
Junichi, thanks for today.
こっちこそ　ありがとう
I should be thanking you.
久しぶりに
楽しいクリスマスだったよ
It's been a while since I've had a fun Christmas.
創設祭に参加するのも
いいもんだね
It wasn't a bad idea to participate in the Founder's Festival.
Really?
ホント？　よかった
Yeah.
That's good.
それにしても　さすがに冷えるな
It's gotten really cold out though.
うん　そうだね
Yeah.
It has.
あッ　なんか空気に
ミントが混ざったみたい
It's like there's mint in the air.
息をするとスーッとする
It feels cool when you breathe in.
ミントねえ
あれ？　イマイチ？
Mint, huh?
Oh?  You didn't like it?
何かの小説で読んで
I read it from a novel and thought it was pretty clever...
うまいこと言うな～って
思ったんだけど
うん　ちょっとは分かる気がするよ
Well, I kinda get it.
But it just sounds weird coming from you, Rihoko.
でも梨穂子の口から
そういうのが出るとはな
何よ～
What's that supposed to mean?
あッ
雪
Snow!
No wonder it's so cold out.
どうりで寒いわけだね
うん
Yeah.
そういえば子供の頃
雪が降ったときにさ
Oh yeah, back then when we were kids, whenever it snowed...
えッ？
Huh?
You'd look right up at the sky with your mouth open, right?
梨穂子　空に向かって
大きな口を開けてたよな
《あ～ん》
《・～オッパイ　パイパイ
おっきいな～》
Boobies, boobies... big boobies...
《うん？　梨穂子　何やってんだよ》
Hmm?  Rihoko, what are you doing?
《おなかがすいたから
雪を食べてるの》
I'm hungry, so I'm eating snow.
《冷たくって　おいしいよ》
It's cold and delicious!
Huh?  Does that really fill you up?
《はあ？　そんなんで
おなかふくれるのか？》
《エヘヘヘ　あ～ん》
Rihoko, you couldn't stop doing that for quite a while.
梨穂子　なかなかあれ
やめなかったんだよな
Geez... it's true that it didn't fill me up, but it tasted nice.
もう　確かにおなかは
ふくれなかったんだけど
でも　おいしかったんだよ
ホントかな
You sure?
ホワイトクリスマスだな
It's a white Christmas.
うん
Yeah.
It's getting cold.
寒くなってきたな　帰ろう
Let's go home.
待って　純一
Wait, Junichi.
This is a Christmas present for you...
これ
クリスマスプレゼントなんだけど
ああ…
手袋？
うん
Gloves?
Yeah.
今年もサンキューな
Thank you again this year.
はめてみていい？
うん
Can I try them on?
Yeah!
あれ？　指が…
Huh?  My fingers...
ちょっと細すぎたかな
Did I make it too thin?
いいよ　きっとはめてるうちに
伸びるだろうから
It's fine.
I'm sure it'll stretch out after a while.
Will it really?
そうかなあ
ほら　ちゃんとあったかいよ
Look, it's nice and warm.
よかった～
That's good.
ほれ
あッ
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
僕　プレゼント
何も用意してなかった
I don't have a present for you.
気にしないで　別にいいから
Don't worry about it.  It's fine.
でも誕生日にもらった
ホッキョクグマのキーホルダーの
But I didn't give you anything in return for the
polar bear keychain you gave me for my birthday...
お返しもしてなかったし
そうだ　何か梨穂子の
欲しいものを言ってくれ
I know.  Tell me what you want, Rihoko.
えッ　欲しいもの？
What I want?
…って突然言われても
思いつかないなあ
I can't really think of anything since you asked right out of the blue...
特にないよ
Nothing in particular.
You don't have to tell me right now.
今すぐじゃなくていいからさ
Yep, okay!
うん　分かった
男の戦いに　終わりはないさ
There is no end to a man's battle.
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
Hey, what should I do, Kanae-chan?
ねえ　どうしよう　香苗ちゃん
What should I ask him for in return for the present?
何がいいと思う？
プレゼントのお返し
ええ～ッ　そんなのムリだよ
What?!  I can't ask for that!
エヘヘヘッ
Kokoro ga kyunto
心がきゅんと
The area around my heart tightens
・～
Sukoshi dake kyunto
少しだけきゅんと
Just a little bit
Shimetsukerareta nara
締め付けられたなら
Since it's tightening like this
Hontou no koi na no kana?
本当の恋なのかな？
Could this be true love?
Hikaru shibafu no ue
光る芝生の上
Didn't we use to play around
Fuzakete nekoronda ne
ふざけて寝転んだね
And lie down on the sunlit grass?
Mujaki datta
無邪気だった
We were so innocent
Osanakatta hibi
幼かった日々
During our childhood days
Demo kokoro no oku de
でも心の奥で
But deep in my heart
Sodatte yuku kanjou wo
育って行く感情を
A feeling was growing
Sukoshi zutsu kizukihajimeteta
少しずつ気づき始めてた
And I slowly came to realize it
Onaji toki wo sugoshita bun dake
同じ時を過ごした分だけ
The more time we spent together
Sunao ni narenakute
素直になれなくて
The less able I was to be honest
Toomawari shita
遠回りした
I did things indirectly
Kokoro de gyutto
心でぎゅっと
My heart tightens
Tonari de sotto dakishimete
隣でそっと抱き締めて
As you gently embrace me
Anata wo mitsumeteru yo
あなたを見つめてるよ
I can't take my eyes off you
Sore wa chiisana koi no hajimari
それは小さな恋の始まり
That's the beginning of this small love of mine
Ima wa mada ienai kedo
今はまだ言えないけど
I can't tell you this just yet
Anata ga suki da yo
あなたが好きだよ
But I love you
Preview
Next episode preview.
Riho-chan, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, Miya-chan.
Here's your present.
They're woolen panties, Miya-chan.
You won't catch a cold with these.
Oh, thank you!
Now I'll feel nice and warm even when it's cold out.
That's right!  Nice and warm!
Nice and warm!
Next episode: "Succession".
Next Episode
Succession
Well then, your present from me will be this meat bun!
Uh, I'm on a diet right now...